hellobc.com 2019-05-07

# Discover BC Legal & Privacy Policy | Super, Natural BC

#### Legal

Please read these terms and conditions of website use carefully before using the HelloBC site. By continuing to use the HelloBC site, you agree to comply with and be bound by all of the terms and conditions set out below. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify these terms and conditions at any time, and such modifications shall be effective immediately upon posting of the modified terms and conditions. You agree to review the terms and conditions periodically to be aware of such modifications and your continued use of the HelloBC site shall be deemed your conclusive acceptance of the terms and conditions as modified from time to time.

#### Booking Accommodation

Destination BC may provide links to tourism businesses that provide accommodations on our Web site. Clicking on such links takes the visitor directly to the subject businesses own Web site, the terms and conditions of which will apply, and Destination British Columbia has no further involvement or responsibility.

#### Endorsment

The information provided on the HelloBC site is for reference only and does not constitute and should not be construed as an endorsement or recommendation of any air carrier, accommodation, restaurant or any other facility, business or event in British Columbia.

#### Content and Revisions

While Destination British Columbia uses reasonable efforts to ensure all information on the HelloBC site is accurate and current, such accuracy and currency cannot be guaranteed and your reliance thereon is at your own risk. All content, including these terms and conditions, is subject to change without notice. We suggest you review these terms and conditions each time you access this website.

#### No Warranty Or Representation

Nothing on this site shall add to or change any contract for products or services you may have with Destination British Columbia, its partners, suppliers or affiliates. Neither Destination British Columbia, its partners, suppliers, affiliates, nor any other party involved in creating, producing or delivering the information on this site is liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential, punitive or other damages whatsoever, arising out of or in connection with your access to or use of this site including, but not limited to, business interruption and loss of use, data, information and profits (regardless of the form of action, including but not limited to contract, negligence or other tortious act). This limitation applies even if Destination British Columbia has been advised of, or foresees, the possibility of any damages occurring. Without limiting the foregoing, everything on this site is provided to you “as is” without representation, warranty or condition of any kind, either express, implied, or statutory including, but not limited to, implied representations, warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, durability, title, non-infringement of intellectual property rights, or inter-operability of products and services.

#### Use Of Information

You agree not to use any information on this site or linked to this site in any claims, proceedings, suits or actions against Destination British Columbia, its partners, suppliers or affiliates.

#### Monitoring

Destination British Columbia assumes no responsibility or liability for content changed without Destination British Columbia’s consent.

#### Links To Other Sites

Throughout this site, Destination British Columbia provides links to other sites for your convenience. These sites are independent from Destination British Columbia and Destination British Columbia does not endorse, control or make any representations, warranties or conditions concerning their contents or links. It is your responsibility to verify any information contained within linked sites before relying on it. Also, the information contained in the links may be changed or updated at any time without notice. Linked sites may have their own terms and conditions that you should locate and review.

#### Copyright

This material is owned by Destination BC Corp. Unless otherwise noted, and protected by copyright law. It may not be reproduced or redistributed without the prior written permission of Destination BC Corp.

#### Trademark

“Super, Natural British Columbia”, “Super, Natural”, “HelloBC”, “Destination British Columbia”, “Visitor Centre” and all other marks appearing on this website are trademarks and/or Official Marks of Destination BC Corp. or are reproduced with permission. All such marks must not be used or reproduced without the written permission of their owner(s).

#### Consent

You hereby authorize Destination British Columbia to collect and retain all relevant information relating to your use of this site. You further authorize any third party to provide Destination British Columbia with such information. This consent is effective on and after today’s date and does not expire.

#### Viruses

Destination British Columbia assumes no responsibility or liability for any damages to, or viruses that may infect, your computer equipment or other property in connection with your access to or use of this site or your downloading of any data, text, images, files or other materials from the site.

#### Right Of Indemnification

You agree to defend, indemnify and hold Destination British Columbia, its partners, suppliers, affiliates and related companies harmless from any and all liabilities, costs and expenses, including reasonable legal fees, related to any violation of these terms and conditions by you, or in connection with your use of the site.

#### Waiver

Destination British Columbia’s failure to insist upon or enforce strict performance of any provision of these terms and conditions shall not be construed as a waiver of any provision or rights contained in these terms and conditions.

#### Governing Laws

The provincial laws of British Columbia and the federal laws of Canada that apply in British Columbia shall govern these terms and conditions. You agree to be bound by the laws of these jurisdictions.

#### Privacy Policy

Destination British Columbia offers a selection of websites, including international websites, designed to help people find information about travel and vacation experiences in British Columbia and participate in a variety of tourism-related services.

We at Destination British Columbia are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers. Any personal information provided to us through our website is collected, used and disclosed in accordance with the British Columbia  _Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act_  and other applicable legislation. What is considered Personal Information under the British Columbia  _Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act_? Under the British Columbia  _Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act_ , personal information includes recorded information about an identifiable individual, such as name, address, phone number, e-mail address and credit card information. Business contact information is not included in the definition of personal information under our provincial legislation. When Destination British Columbia collects personal information, we identify the:

  * purpose for collecting the personal information,
  * legal authority for collecting it, and
  * title, business phone number, business address and e-mail address of an employee who can answer questions you may have about the collection of information.

#### What Personal Information We Collect and How We Use It

When someone visits one of our websites, our web server automatically collects a limited amount of standard information essential to the operation, security and evaluation of the Destination British Columbia website. This information helps us to make our site more useful to visitors and includes the:

  * Internet domain and Internet Protocol (IP) address from computers that access our website,
  * type of browser and operating system used to access our site,
  * date and time our site is accessed,
  * pages visited,
  * address of any websites linked to, and
  * content downloaded from our site.

While some of this information does not identify who people are, other information (e.g. Internet domain names or the IP addresses of internet service providers) may provide identification. The extent of personal identification depends on the naming standards followed by the internet service provider. You may wish to check with your provider to inquire about their policies and practices in this regard. Destination British Columbia does not use this information to identify individuals who visit our website unless required to do so as part of an internal investigation or other law enforcement purpose.

Any personal information collected via our website (e.g. web forms) is done in compliance with BC’s privacy legislation and is considered necessary for providing services offered by our organization. There is always an option of whether or not to provide us with personal information. Your decision not to participate in electronic service delivery activities will not impair your ability to browse our website. However, it may limit the use of certain website features. The personal information provided to us is used for the purpose for which it was collected or for a use consistent with that purpose. For example, personal information may be used to: send information about British Columbia that we believe will be of interest (based on a confidential personal profile); contact about upcoming vacation opportunities; respond to inquiries; provide requested materials; obtain feedback on vacation experiences; or assist with the use of our website. In most cases, we try to obtain explicit consent before these activities will occur. At any time, anyone may request that we stop communicating by either updating their user profile or contacting us directly.

#### Storage, Access and Disclosure of Your Personal Information

Destination British Columbia and our service providers (for support reasons), may store or access your Personal Information which may resides outside of Canada. In certain circumstances, we may need to disclose your personal information to our service providers in order to facilitate the operation of our website, database, email marketing software or processing of payment transactions. In some cases, these service providers may reside outside of Canada. Before any personal information is disclosed, all recipient organizations must agree to protect the privacy of personal information in a contractual manner consistent with our policy and compliant with BC’s Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act.

#### Security of Your Information

Destination British Columbia is obligated to protect personal information by making reasonable security arrangements against such risks as unauthorized access, collection, use, disclosure or disposal. Security measures, such as the use of SSL encryption, have been integrated into the design, implementation and day-to-day operating practices as part our commitment to protect the information we hold.

The personal information submitted is secure once it reaches the Destination British Columbia server. In transit between a computer and the server, all information is secured using SSL encryption, which the web browser typically denotes using a lock icon.

#### Links to Other Websites

The Destination British Columbia website also provides links to external websites that offer information on tourism-related products and services. These sites may be operated by other government agencies, non-profit organizations or private businesses. Destination British Columbia is not responsible for the content and privacy practices of external websites. We encourage users to review the privacy policy for each external site before submitting any personal information.

#### Blogs / Tips for Travellers

The Destination British Columbia Blogs page enables online visitors to publicly share information about their personal travel and vacation experiences. If interested, a visitor can opt to become a registered Destination British Columbia blog user and submit stories for posting consideration. Submitters must accept detailed Terms and Conditions as part of the registration process. These terms stipulate that submitters must have obtained all necessary consent(s) prior to submitting a story or photograph as any personal information included in a submission could become publicly available on the Internet if selected by Destination British Columbia. Personal information collected for the purpose of blog user registration is protected in accordance with the  _Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act_ , and not disclosed outside of Destination British Columbia. We reserve the right to reject or edit the content of submissions in order to protect individual privacy. Submitters and/or the individuals whose personal information appears in a blog submission have the right, at any time, to request removal of a story or image from Destination British Columbia’s Blogs page and/or flickr.com.

#### Contests

Destination British Columbia runs a variety of contests on the HelloBC.com website that our online visitors can optionally enter. We use online contest entry forms to collect personal information deemed necessary for your participation in a contest. While certain information is mandatory for participation, most information is optional. Contest entry forms differentiate between the two so that you are aware of what information is needed, and what information you need not provide in order to participate. As part of the contest entry process, we may provide an opportunity for you to give Destination British Columbia permission to contact you in the future. Giving your permission for future contact is completely optional, and does not impact your ability to participate in a contest.

When you provide us with your personal information to enter a contest, we retain and use it in accordance with the  _Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act_. Your information is only used for the purpose for which it was collected (e.g. to support your participation in a contest), or for a use consistent with that purpose (e.g. to allow us to conduct tourism-related research or surveys, or provide you with information on other contests or tourism opportunities with your consent). Our objective is to measure the success of our tourism marketing campaigns, and help us understand the characteristics and travel preferences of our consumers in order to serve them to the best of our ability.

We work closely with our Information Technology team to ensure the contest entry data we receive is securely stored and may only be accessed by authorized staff and approved contest service providers. Any service provider that we engage for a given contest must agree to and comply with the BC Government’s terms and conditions for protecting personal information in order to do business with us. Effectively safeguarding all personal information in our custody is of paramount importance to Destination British Columbia.

#### Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of data that web pages place in devices (e.g., computers or mobile phones) to assist in returning to that page. Destination British Columbia uses cookies to track activities on our website to help us identify what tourism-related products and services consumers are interested in, so that we may continually work towards providing useful and relevant content, and to provide a more personalized experience. It is possible to change the settings on a web browser to deny cookies or to warn when cookies will be deposited.

We may allow our service provider to place cookies on your devices and collect the IP address of your devices, which provides our service provider with your general location data. Our service provider may use this data to serve you with advertisements, on our website or elsewhere online, and to report to us on an aggregated basis on the effectiveness of our advertisements at inspiring tourists to travel to British Columbia and provide us with statistics on visitors of British Columbia (for instance, where they are coming from). In order to do so, our service provider may combine your IP address with other information that our service provider has obtained from other sources, as permitted by law.

If you wish to opt out of third party cookies that allow us to serve advertisements and collect aggregate information on arrivals to British Columbia [click here](http://dc.arrivalist.com/optout/). If you opt-out, our service provider will also cease collecting information about your IP address from other sources.

#### Google Maps

Destination British Columbia uses a third-party service for locator maps. See the Google Map [Terms and Conditions](http://www.google.com/intl/en_ca/help/terms_maps.html).

#### How Long Information Is Retained

The length of information retention varies in relation to the nature of the service provided. We keep information for the length of time necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected. Destination British Columbia manages the information it collects in accordance with government records retention schedules and other legislative requirements.

#### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

Destination British Columbia may, from time to time, review and revise its privacy practices and our website privacy policy.

#### Who Can I Contact About the Destination British Columbia Privacy Policy or the Collection/Use of Personal Information?

General questions or comments about our online privacy policy can be directed to:

Neil McInnes, Chief Financial Officer  
Destination British Columbia  
(778)572-5251  
[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

#### Where Can I Find Information on British Columbia’s  _Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act_?

For information relating to British Columbia’s  _Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act_ , please refer to the Government of British Columbia website at: <http://www.gov.bc.ca/citz/iao/>
